const flashcardsContent = [
  { question: "Chlorate", answer: "ClO₃⁻", typeAnswer: "ClO3-" },
  { question: "Chlorite", answer: "ClO₂⁻", typeAnswer: "ClO2-" },
  { question: "Perchlorate", answer: "ClO₄⁻", typeAnswer: "ClO4-"},
  { question: "Hypochlorite", answer: "ClO⁻", typeAnswer: "ClO-"},
  { question: "Nitrite", answer: "NO₂⁻", typeAnswer: "NO2-"},
  { question: "Nitrate", answer: "NO₃⁻", typeAnswer: "NO3-"},
  { question: "Sulfate", answer: "SO₄²⁻", typeAnswer: "SO4(2-)"},
  { question: "Sulfite", answer: "SO₃²⁻", typeAnswer: "SO3(2-)" },
  { question: "Hydrogen Sulfate", answer: "HSO₄⁻", typeAnswer: "HSO4-" },
  { question: "Hydrogen Sulfite", answer: "HSO₃⁻", typeAnswer: "HSO3-" },
  { question: "Phosphate", answer: "PO₄³⁻", typeAnswer: "PO4(3-)" },
  { question: "Hydrogen Phosphate", answer: "HPO₄²⁻", typeAnswer: "HPO4(2-)" },
  { question: "Dihydrogen Phosphate", answer: "H₂PO₄⁻", typeAnswer: "H2PO4-" },
  { question: "Carbonate", answer: "CO₃²⁻", typeAnswer: "CO3(2-)" },
  { question: "Bicarbonate", answer: "HCO₃⁻", typeAnswer: "HCO3-" },
  { question: "Permanganate", answer: "MnO₄⁻", typeAnswer: "MnO4-" },
  { question: "Chromate", answer: "CrO₄²⁻", typeAnswer: "CrO4(2-)" },
  { question: "Dichromate", answer: "Cr₂O₇²⁻", typeAnswer: "Cr2O7(2-)" },
  { question: "Ammonium", answer: "NH₄⁺", typeAnswer: "NH4+" },
  { question: "Hydronium", answer: "H₃O⁺", typeAnswer: "H3O+" },
  { question: "Acetate", answer: "CH₃CO²⁻", typeAnswer: "CH3CO(2-)" },
  { question: "Cyanide", answer: "CN⁻", typeAnswer: "CN-" },
  { question: "Azide", answer: "N₃⁻", typeAnswer: "N3-" },
  { question: "Peroxide", answer: "O₂²⁻", typeAnswer: "O2(2-)" },
  { question: "Hydroxide", answer: "OH⁻", typeAnswer: "OH(-)" },
];

export default flashcardsContent;